cscsnigeriaplc.com 2014-06-03

# Central Securities Clearing System Limited

This statement discloses the information practices for the CSCS website, including what type of information is gathered and tracked, how the information is used, and with whom the information is shared. In general, you can visit CSCS Plc on the internet without telling us who you are and without giving any personal information about yourself. There are times, however, when we may need information from you to better serve you.

###   
Personal information

You may choose to give us personal information in a variety of situations. For example, you may want to give us information, such as your name and address or e-mail address, to correspond with you or to provide you with a subscription. You may give us a description of your education and work experience in connection with a job opening at CSCS that you wish to be considered for. We intend to let you know how we will use such information before we collect it from you; if you tell us that you do not want us to use this information to make further contact with you beyond fulfilling your requests, we will respect your wishes.

The following paragraphs describe in more detail how CSCS may use your personal information.

###   
Marketing use

The information you provide to CSCS through the website may be used by CSCS only for marketing purposes. Before we use it, however, we will offer you the opportunity to choose whether or not to have your information used in this way.

###   
CSCS Careers pages

In connection with a job application or inquiry, whether advertised on the CSCS website or otherwise, you may provide us with information about yourself, such as a resume or curriculum vitae. We may use this information throughout CSCS entities for the purpose of employment consideration or your inquiry. Except where you tell us not to, we will keep the information for future consideration.

###   
Information security and quality

We intend to protect your personal information and to maintain its quality. We implement appropriate measures and processes to help us to keep your information secure and to maintain its quality.

###   
Supplementing information

From time to time we may supplement information you give us via the CSCS website with information from other sources, such as information validating your address or other available information about businesses. This is to help us maintain the accuracy of the information we collect and to help us provide a better service.

###   
Cookies

We sometimes collect non-identifiable information from visits to our Web sites to help us provide better customer service. For example, we keep measuring visitors’ activities on this site and CSCS may use this data to analyse trends and statistics and to help us provide better customer service.

We collect the information we mentioned in the previous paragraphs through the use of various technologies, including one called "cookies". A cookie is a piece of data that a website can send to your browser, which may then be stored on your computer as an anonymous tag that identifies your computer but not you. You can set your browser to notify you before you receive a cookie, giving you the chance to decide whether to accept it. You can also set your browser to turn off cookies. If you do so, however, some pages may not work properly.

###   
Links to non-CSCS sites

The CSCS website contains links to other websites. CSCS is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of those other websites.
